『昇らない太陽』—　The Pillows
她-她-她从哪里来?!
W-W-Where did she come from?!
酷——美—— 她来了！
Hi...do...mi -- Aah! -- is here!
对了！我们今天也要吃掉彼此呢！
Oh, yeah! We're gonna devour each other today!
我和我的朋友们！
Me and my friends!
我的朋友们就是
And by friends I mean my former classmates,
我从来没有说过话的老同学！
whom I never had a single conversation with!
好棒！
Yatta!
呃 喂？怎么这样！
Uh, hey? How awful!
我的朋友一个都没来！
None of my friends are here!
这样我不就没法感受被吃掉的痛苦了吗?!
How am I supposed to feel the pain of being eaten now?!
将我的体内和外界分隔开的
The single layer of skin that divides the inside
那一层皮肤 我想让它被剥落！
of my body from the outside, I want it peeled off!
我想让它被撕下 被啃食掉！
I want it clawed off! I want it gnawed off.
我好想让我的皮肤被猛地扯开
I just want the whole thing ripped open with one swift tear!
我被撕裂的皮肤所感受到的冰冷的空气是世界的温度
The cold air that I feel on my cracked and torn skin is the temperature of the world!
喂！酷美！酷美！
Hey, Hidomi! Hidomi!
我跟你说过要当心骑 Vespa 的女人！
I told you to watch out for the Vespa woman!
我让你留神的！
I told you to be careful.
为什么不听我的话！你应该记着我的警告！
Why didn't you listen to me?! You should've heeded my warning!
小心！
Hey, look out!
看！
Pay attention!
我受不了了
I can't take it!
打水漂
本字幕由 SweetSub 制作　仅做交流学习之用途
翻校：ピロピラ ピロコ　其它：tastySugar
晴子老师 你真是太棒了！
Miss Haruko, you are seriously the best!
Yoohoo 男生们？
Yoohoo? Male students?
有没有人愿意帮老师涂防晒霜？
Does one of you boys wanna help their teacher put on sunscreen?
-来了！ -等等
-Coming! -Hold on.
喂 森 看看时间 你没有忘了吧？
Hey, Mori? Look at the time. Aren't you forgetting something?
你不是说你的女朋友马上要来吗？
Didn't you say your girlfriend was coming soon?
你跟我们说过你有个女朋友的
You told us that you had a girlfriend,
我们来沙滩上就是因为这个
and we came all the way to the beach 'cause of it.
可一定要让我们见到她
So we'd better get to meet her.
那必须的！我的朋友们！
Of course! Fear not, my fellow friends!
我只是忘了时间而已！
I merely lost track of the time!
跟我走 这边！
This way, men! Follow me!
好吧 云雀弄 你来帮我涂
All right, fine. Hibaji. You'll have to do it.
你来涂也行 仁由
I'm fine with you doing it, as well, Jinyu.
同志们！
Comrades!
这是我的女朋友
This is my girlfriend.
来认识一下爱子
Come say hello to Aiko.
快 跟他们打个招呼
Go on, say something to them!
初次见面
Uh, nice to meet you.
我和森正在交往中
I'm dating your good friend Mori.
我的名字是爱子
My name's Aiko.
啊 好害羞
Ah! I'm so embarrassed!
她好完美！淑女！
She's perfect! Such a lady!
她不喝酒 不说脏话 也不出汗！
She doesn't drink, swear, or sweat!
难以置信吧 这么热的天！
Can you believe it?! This hot and no sweat!
抱歉我想问一下
Excuse me?
你为什么会想和森交往？
What was it that made you wanna date Mori?
那个…
Oh. Well...
因为我非常喜欢他
because I really like him.
啊 好害羞
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
你手里拿的是啥玩意？
What is that thing you've been holding?
这个？这…就是一个花盆
Oh, this? T-This is just a flower pot.
这我知道 但是你为什么会拿着花盆？
I figured, but why do you have it?
这是一株用于情感支持的植物
It's an emotional support plant.
真的有用吗？
Does it work?
这不是很可爱吗?!
Isn't that just cute?!
别这么说！好害羞！
Don't say that! It's embarrassing!
也许看不出来 但是这盆植物还挺贵的
It may not look like it, but this plant was expensive.
好吧 我还真看不出来
Yeah? I would've never guessed.
啊！好可爱！
Ah! So cute!
油乎乎的！多少防晒指数的？
So oily! What SPF was that?!
呀 这是助晒油
Oh. This is tanning oil.
这是什么?!
It's what?
哼 对我还有意见
Still holding a grudge, I see.
比起过去三个月
Just for the past three months.
你对我们的缠扰
Ever since you've been stalking me.
这不算什么
This is nothing.
你想要的 你已经得到过一次了
You've already gotten what you wanted once before.
是时候结束了
It's time you quit.
放手吧
Just give up.
没门
No way.
我需要满足心愿才能完成——
I need to fulfill my wish in order to fulfill my --
好害羞！
How embarrassing!
攻击——
Attack number...
一号
ichi!
好害羞！
So embarrassing!
不如现在先停战吧？
So, why don't we call a truce for now?
不管你们准备好没有 你们的老师要参战了！
Ready or not, your teacher's coming!
那个女人…
That woman over there...
Here's the balls!
球来了！
她想要什么？
What does she want?
球来了！
Here comes the balls!
那个女人和我相同
That woman's the same as me.
『Thank you, my twilight 』—　The Pillows
接球！
Receive!
哔 哔 哔
Bip, bip, bip!
下一个谁来？
Who wants to go next?!
所以 仁由
So, uh, Jinyu...
你想要的是什么？
What is it that you want?
我曾经和一个很棒的人在一起
I was once with someone amazing.
他巨大 强大 那样令人不可思议
He was big, strong, and just simply amazing.
和他在一起 我可以在宇宙中自由翱翔 永不停止
With him, one can fly around anywhere in space forever.
但是后来他突然消失了
But then he suddenly disappeared.
他抛弃了我
He abandoned me.
结果到头来 我根本无法与他相比对等
Turns out, in the end, I just wasn't his equal.
我不能满足他 单靠我是不够的…
I'm not enough for him. Not by myself...
然而 我们还是继续寻找他
And yet, we still continue to look for him.
「我们」？
We?
来呀！
Bring it on!
晴子老师也在找吗？
Miss Haruko is searching, too?
追寻只是因为无法抓获
You chase something simply because you can't catch it.
想要触碰 只是因为知道自己触碰不到
Want to touch it, 'cause you know you can't.
你也一定有过这样的经历吧
You must have experienced something like that in your life?
你在问我吗？
You're asking me?
酷美真正想要的是什么呢？
What is that Hidomi really wants?
我…
Well...
实话说 我没有什么想要的
truth is, there's really nothing that I want.
不敢相信你能接到球！
Can't believe you could play like that!
『天使みたいにキミは立ってた』—　The Pillows
真可谓是青春啊
The blue spring of adolescence.
也许这是我们的友谊的延伸？
Perhaps this is an extension of our friendship?
迟来的青春 你觉得呢？
Delayed adolescence, if you will?
我不介意你对我们的关系有新的看法
I'm content with you changing your mind about our relationship.
但这不意味着你可以插手酷美的事情
But regardless, it still doesn't mean that you can have Hidomi.
继续争斗毫无意义
No point in fighting anymore.
真的如此吗？
Huh is that so
洗脑抑制机制
Brainwashing suppression mechanism...
他们提前采取了措施
They took extra measures ahead of time.
你不觉得很赞吗？ 我们在一起多开心啊！
Isn't this just great? Aren't we having the best time?
你觉得我们能堆多高？
How high do you think we can make it?
随便你在哪里挖
-Dig wherever you want.
还有…
-By the way...
…我不明白这样有什么好玩的
...I'm not really seeing the fun in all of this.
啊！该去尿尿了！该走的时候就不要等
Ah! Tinkle time! When you gotta go, you gotta go.
我走了！
And I'm going!
你不算去游泳吗？
So, are you not planning on swimming?
哈？不
Huh? No.
都已经到沙滩上了 你却不想游泳吗？
Oh. You're not, even though we came to the beach to swim?
-那你呢？-嗯？
-And what about you. -Excuse me?
你带了泳衣吗？
Did you bring your swimsuit?
这不是我们事先说好的内容
That's not what we agreed to this time.
你们看到了吗？
Did you see that just now?!
喂！爱子！
Hey, Aiko!
看到我有多厉害了吗？
Did you witness my awesomeness?!
等下 云雀弄在哪里？
Wait a sec. Where's Hibajiri?
不行 找不到她
No use. I can't find her.
我想不出她能去哪里
I wonder where she could've gone.
晴子老师也不见了
Miss Haruko is missing, as well.
也许她们没跟我们说就自己回家了？
Maybe they went home without telling us?
如果她们没有回家怎么办?!
And what do we do if they didn't?!
再找一次！把沙滩从头到尾再搜一遍！
Let's look again! Do one more sweep of the beach!
森…
Mori…
我必须回家了
I'm gonna need to go home soon.
啊！对不起！我忘了你的那件事
Huh? Oh, right! Sorry! I forgot about your thing.
对对对对
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
我去去就回 把爱子送到车站
-I'll be right back. I'm just gonna walk Aiko to the station.
那好吧
-Oh. Okay. -Thank you.
谢谢 你人真好
You're such a nice person.
小菜一碟 哈哈哈
It's no biggie!
我把话说清楚 我要收加班费！
Just so you know, I'll be charging you overtime!
我很抱歉
I am sorry about that
-钱呢  -呃 在这
- Give it.  - Uh, here.
-拿好  -一定
- Hold this. - Sure.
我扮演的角色还对你的口味吗？
So, was the character I created to your liking?
是的 非常完美 你超棒的
Yes, it was perfect! You were fantastic!
火车即将离开站台
The train will be leaving the station momentarily.
OK  正好
Okay. It's all there.
你们男生觉得害羞怯懦的女孩子很可爱 是吗？
You boys think it's so cute when girls are all shy and timid, am I right?
对了 那盆草你留着吧
Oh, by the way, the plant's yours to keep.
这是给你的礼物！
A present for you!
哦 谢谢！你真——
Oh. Thank you. That is so ni--
才怪
No, it's not.
你就假装是用信封里的东西换了那个
Let's just pretend that we exchanged what's in this envelope for that.
我可不想让别人知道我在搞租赁女友的生意
I wouldn't want people finding out that I'm running a rent-a-date.
所以说…我从你那里买了这个
So... I bought this from you.
拜拜 或者随便你
Bye. Or whatever.
马！
Maa!
『白い夏と緑の自転車 赤い髪と黒いギター』—　The Pillows
-当你还小的时候… -谁?!
-When you were a kid... -Who's there?!
你有没有试着画过自己和家人一起去看烟花
Did you ever try drawing a picture of going to see fireworks with your family,
但却画不出来？
only to fail?
仁由 是你吗？
It's Jinyu, right?
告诉我 酷美—我是说 云雀弄和你在一起吗？
Tell me, is Hidomi -- I mean, is Hibajiri with you?
你想要画出你看见的无数光点
You try to draw the countless specks of light that you saw,
但是重现夜空的唯一方法
but the only way to recreate the night sky
就是用黑色铅笔把一切都涂上颜色
is to color everything in with a black pencil.
它们照亮了夜空
They were lighting up that dark sky
绚烂夺目
and they were so colorful and beautiful.
你在说什么?!你怎么不——
What are you talking about?! Why won't you--
所有美丽的事物最终都将消逝
All beautiful things eventually fade away.
哦 第一颗星
Oh, the first star.
摸来摸去 摸来摸去
Goodie. Goodie, goodie, goodie
请住手
Please stop.
我们进一步互相了解对方吧
Let's get to know each other better.
住手！
Stop it!
是这里吗？
Is it here?
不要 住手 求求你
No. Stop, please.
行了 笑话我吧
Go on, laugh at me.
别笑了！
Stop laughing!
哎呀
Oh, my.
看来你原本是打算出来好好玩的
Looks like you were planning on having fun today.
帮我个忙吧
Help me out here.
告诉我应该摸哪里 才能让你溢出
Just tell me where to hit you, so you'll overflow.
溢出？
Overflow?
你为什么要这么做 晴子老师
What are you doing, Miss Haruko?!
什么 居然是从这家伙里面出来的？
What? It's coming out of that one?
我不知道你是什么东西 但是…
I don't know what the hell you are, but...
去救云雀弄！
...go save Hibajiri!
真是悲惨得不忍直视 森！
It was too painful to watch, Mori!
拜托你别哭了行不行？
Will you please stop crying?
你让我感觉更可悲了
You're just making me feel even more pathetic.
不！
No!
上帝啊 为什么？为什么会这样？
Oh, God, why? Why is this happening?
喂 爱子
Hey, Aiko?
你知道这个房间的花盆到哪里去了吗？
Do you know what happened to the flower pot that was in this room?
不晓得
No clue.
这里是代号眼罩
This is code name Eye Patch.
有新的情况吗？-我这里有点小麻烦
Do you have an update? -I have a slight problem.
什么麻烦？
What?
I can't locate the "flower pot."
我找不到「花盆」了
滚你——
Son-of-a...!
酷美——
Hidomi...
听着 井出
Listen, Ide.
只有你可以救酷美
You're the only one who can save Hidomi.
在后座
Back here.
你怎么搞成这样？
What happened to you?
算了
Never mind.
我们还有其他事情要做
We have more important things to deal with.
酷美在那个东西里面 那不正常 对吧?!
Hidomi is inside of that thing! That's not normal, right?!
实话说 最近不正常的事情有不少
Truth be told, there have been plenty of things that haven't been normal lately.
但这次不一样 这是不可接受的！
But this is different. This is unacceptable!
拜托了仁由！你得做点什么！
Please! You have to do something, Jinyu!
如果你画不出烟花 那么…
If you are unable to draw fireworks, well then...
啥？
What?
就向天空发射烟花吧
Try shooting one in the air.
再试一次  多少次都行直到成功为止！
Do it again! As many times as you need!
我改主意了  你应该是烟花才对
On second thought, maybe you should be the firework instead?
『Freebee Honey』—　The Pillows
啊 很好
Ah, yeah!
酷毙了
This is amazing!
啊！逮到你了！
Ah! Got you now!
喂！云雀弄！
Hey! Hibajiri!
云雀弄！云雀弄！
Hibajiri! Hibajiri!
该死！我该怎么做?!
Shit! What am I supposed to do?!
唔…她还没被满足
Hmm. She doesn't have enough yet.
晴子老师
Miss Haruko.
骄傲…？撒娇…？
A tundra Sundera
傲娇？唔…
Tsundere? Hmm.
这个女孩是那种类型吧？
This girl is that type, isn't she?
我说得没错吧？
Am I right?
闭嘴
Shut up.
云雀弄！啊！
Hibajiri! Ah!
云雀弄！云雀弄！
Hibajiri! Hibajiri!
我只想要你能醒过来
I just want you to wake up.
喊她的名字可没有用
Calling her name won't help.
让你靠谱的老师来吧
Leave it up to your good old teach.
住手！
Stop it!
那就取下她的耳机
Then take off her headphones.
去呀 别害羞
Go on, don't be shy.
不要担心
No need to worry.
你的声音会传递给她的
Your voice will reach her.
别做！别被骗了！
It's a trick! Don't do it!
你能够得到的
You can reach it.
这在她的身体深处
It's deep inside of her.
不如我们一起来 OK?
Why don't we do it together, OK?
我不用你帮忙！我自己来！
I don't need your help! I'll do it myself!
『Fool on the Planet』—　The Pillows
云雀弄！喂！云雀弄！该死的！
Hibajiri! Hey! Hibajiri! Dammit!
我让你不要那样做的！
I told you not to do that!
如果你…
If you...
应急系统被激活了
The emergency system has been activated.
没有任何办法停下它
There's nothing you can do to stop it.
天呐
Ah, geez.
可恶 那些混蛋 真够狡猾的
Damn, they're so sneaky. Those bastards.
这都是因为你试图诱惑那个男生
This is all because you tried to tempt that guy.
没错 晴子老师试图…
That's right, Miss Haruko tried to...
云雀弄！
Hibajiri!
她…她从哪里来？
Whe…where she comes from.......
是…是我 酷 酷美
It's -- it's me, Hi-Hidomi...
我来了
is... right here.
什么？喂！
What? Hey!
云雀弄！我不明白！
Hibajiri! I don't understand!
求求你 醒过来 说点什么！
Please, wake up! Say something!
告诉我这幅景象是怎么回事？
Tell me what's wrong with this picture?
看起来就像 就像…
Take a look. It's like...it's like...
说什么都行！你的话到底什么意思！
Anything! What do you mean by that.....
对不起 我觉得都是我的错
I'm sorry! I feel like this is all my fault!
我想这也许就是所谓青春吧
I guess that's what they call adolescence.
求求你 把眼睛睁开 云雀弄！
Please open your eyes! Please, Hibajiri!
只剩一个选择 拉哈路
Only one option left, Raharu.
看来只能正面突破了
I supposed I'll just have to bust on in.
没错 我们的目的也许不同
Right. While our objectives may be different,
我们却有着同一个目标
our target remains the same.
Medical Mechanica
Medical Mechanica.